<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Victor Fleury</title>
    <link>http://victorfleury.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Victor Fleury</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with &amp;#10084; using hugo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:19:18 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://victorfleury.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interfacing C&#43;&#43; and Python</title>
      <link>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/cpp_interfacing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:19:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/cpp_interfacing/</guid>
      <description>How to interface C++ code with Python ? This is a quick how-to for :
 Installing pybind on WSL (which should work on Linux in general) Writing a small piece of code in C++ Compiling and building the lib to expose in Python Using said lib.  The purpose of this is mainly to play with C++ and Python and see how the two can be interfaced so you can benefit from the speed of C++ via Python and vice-versa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing drag and drop in Python using Qt</title>
      <link>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/qt_drag_n_drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 20:55:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/qt_drag_n_drop/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I needed to implement a drag and drop behaviour to reorder widgets in a tool and this article is just a reminder to my future self on how to do it and what caveats I should remember avoiding.
I had to implement this using a model/view approach with Qt.
Here is the official doc : Qt Model/View 
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started ! So first let&amp;rsquo;s look at what the model needs in order to implement this correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grab a nice wallpaper every day</title>
      <link>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/grab_photo_of_the_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 18:45:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victorfleury.github.io/posts/grab_photo_of_the_day/</guid>
      <description>This is a small tool I developed to grab the latest image from the National Geographic&amp;rsquo;s website and build a nice photo library of wallpapers.
It is always nice to start the day with a new nice wallpaper.
With a small cron job, it is then ran every day automatically.
There is no API is provided, so we must scrap the webpage for the information we want.
But with a simple bit of Python it is quite easy to grab these images.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>